campusexplorer.com 2018-12-27

# Campus Explorer Privacy Policy

At Campus Explorer, Inc., we continue to develop technological enhancements for students, families, schools and our partners. We are committed to excellence in customer service, and your privacy is important to us. This is the Privacy Policy for all Campus Explorer, Inc. websites, including the website currently located at www.campusexplorer.com (collectively "Site" or "Sites"). For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Sites” also includes the portion of certain third party websites that consists of application forms (“Forms”) that we provide to such websites and through which we may collect information from users, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of such third party websites, other than the Forms. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and protect Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) when you use the Site and your choices for managing your information preferences. By using the Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy and the Campus Explorer Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 9, 2015.

### Personal Information

Campus Explorer will collect personally identifying information such as your name, address, email address, social security number and similar identifying information ("Personal Information"), if you provide it to us through one of our Sites or online services. For example, if you choose to register on a Site in order to utilize an online service that requires you to log in, Campus Explorer may collect basic Personal Information. You may verify, correct, update, or change your registration information at any time by e-mailing us at [privacy@campusexplorer.com](mailto:privacy@campusexplorer.com) or click here to log in to your account.

The Site enables you to voluntarily provide Personal Information to third parties such as college or university admissions departments. If you choose to submit an online loan application, we may collect information such as your Social Security Number, and that of your endorser or co-borrower, if applicable, date of birth, driver's license number, phone number, and references required for the completion of a student loan application. We may combine any Personal Information collected through the Sites with other information that we obtain about you, your computer, and/or device from other companies and sources, including third-party data suppliers and public databases. Information we may collect from other sources may include name, postal address, email address and telephone number, demographic data, such as age, gender, and income level, your interests and purchase behavior; publicly-visible data, such as your posts and submissions to blogs, video-sharing services, and other interactive forums, and other navigation data, such as web sites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on.

### Non-Personal Information

We automatically collect information that does not personally identify you as an individual to help us understand how our users use the Site. Like most websites, we automatically collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser you used to visit the Site, the time you visited the Site, which Web pages you visited on the Site, and other anonymous Site usage data. We call this type of information "Non-Personal Information".

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Site. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, including, without limitation, marketing and advertising campaigns.

### How we use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information

We use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for internal purposes, such as to notify you of new or relevant products or services, to send service notifications, to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Site, to conduct research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Site, and to provide more relevant products, services, and advertisements on or through the Site. Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may be combined with data collected from other sources so that we may further improve the relevance of products, services, and advertisements offered to you or on or through the Site.

When you request information regarding colleges, universities or lenders, we may provide your Personal Information to colleges, universities or lenders, or to third parties acting on behalf of colleges, universities or lenders. We may also provide your Personal Information to our educational marketing partners or other marketing partners that provide products and services which may be of interest to you. The colleges, universities or lenders, or such third parties acting on their behalf, our educational marketing partners, or other marketing partners may communicate with you, and their use of your data is governed by their privacy policies. When you provide us with your telephone number, you acknowledge that we or the colleges, universities or lenders, or such third parties acting on their behalf, our educational marketing partners, or other marketing partners may contact you at that number and may do so using an automatic telephone dialing system and/or an artificial or prerecorded voice. If you subsequently request that we not contact you at that number, we will honor your request as soon as reasonably practicable. If your contact information has already been provided to colleges, universities or lenders, or such third parties acting on their behalf, our educational marketing partners, or other marketing partners, then you should specifically make a request to such parties. You may request and receive a disclosure providing a list of categories of Personal Information shared, during the immediately preceding calendar year, with our marketing partners, and the names and addresses of our marketing partners with whom such information was shared. You may request such a disclosure by emailing us at [privacy@campusexplorer.com](mailto:privacy@campusexplorer.com).

From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as credit card processing, advertising, analytics tools, widget providers, data management services, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information reasonably necessary for them to perform these services. 

We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personal Information regarding the Site (e.g., number of visits, page views, number of registered members who reside in a particular geographic location, etc.). However, such information does not identify you individually.

We may work with third-party marketing and advertising companies including Yahoo! Inc. and Google Inc. which may use information about your visit to the Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Site and on third-party websites. From the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons or pixel tags. We may use Google Analytics and the Doubleclick cookie to serve ads based on a user’s prior visit to the Site. Users may opt out of the Doubleclick cookie by visiting [this page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). Users may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting [this page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party advertisement serving company may collect from you. For more information about ad cookies and companies that provide users the ability to "opt-out" of the collection of information from such cookies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We may share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Campus Explorer. In the event that Campus Explorer is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in connection with such transaction.

In certain instances we may disclose Personal Information and Non-Personal Information when we believe it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities in order to protect Campus Explorer or our users or when we believe that the law or legal process requires such disclosure.

### Communication Tools; Public Areas

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about one of our Sites, Campus Explorer will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to view the article that you are sending them. Campus Explorer does not store this information, and it is for the sole purpose of sending the one-time e-mail.

Please be advised that, whenever you voluntarily post information to any community or interactive areas of the Site, such information can and may be accessed by the public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

### Confidentiality and Security

Information collected on or through the Site is stored on servers using encryption technology. Campus Explorer strives to employ industry standard security procedures to prevent unauthorized access to user information. However, no data security measures can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information you provide, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide, and you do so at your own risk.

### Passwords

There is a link available on the Campus Explorer log-in page to enable you to change your password at any time. If you forget your password, there is a link on the log-in page that will enable you to enter your Username or e-mail address with which you originally registered. When you submit this information, if your information matches what Campus Explorer has recorded for you, your username and password will be e-mailed to you.

### Children's Privacy Statement

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

### Opting Out of Email

If you do not want to receive email from Campus Explorer, please follow the steps outlined below to submit an opt-out request:

  * If you are registered with campusexplorer.com you can change your preferences in your Profile. Sign in to view your Profile, click on “edit email preferences,” and then click the “Unsubscribe” button.
  * To unsubscribe from an email, click the link to unsubscribe in the next e-mail you receive from us.
  * To unsubscribe offline, you may contact us by phone at 310-579-2725, or write to:  

Campus Explorer  
12555 W. Jefferson Blvd, Suite 202  
Los Angeles, CA 90066

### Do Not Track Signals

We do not currently respond to browser based “do not track” signals.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Campus Explorer may, from time to time, amend this Privacy Policy by posting the amended Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Site.

### Contact information

If you have any questions about this policy please contact:  
Customer Privacy  
Campus Explorer  

### Data Transfers

Please note that the Services are intended solely and exclusively for residents of the United States, its territories and possessions ("U.S.") while they are located in the U.S. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy is specifically directed only towards residents of the U.S. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S. and you use the Site contrary to our Terms of Use, you do so at your own risk and initiative, and are responsible for compliance with any applicable local and national laws. Please be aware that any information you submit to us will be transferred to and processed in the U.S and subject to U.S. law, which may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence. By using the Site and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage and processing of information to and in the U.S., and waive any claims that may arise under your own local and national laws.

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are resident of California, you may request and receive a disclosure providing a list of categories of personal information shared, during the immediately preceding calendar year, with other businesses for their direct marketing purposes, and the names and addresses of the other businesses with whom such information was shared. You may request such a disclosure by emailing us at [privacy@campusexplorer.com](mailto:privacy@campusexplorer.com).

For more information, visit the [California Privacy homepage](http://www.privacy.ca.gov/privacy_laws/index.shtml)
